<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.knime.htmltablereader.feature"
      label="HTML Table Reader"
      version="1.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Maxson Jordan"
      os="linux,macosx,win32"
      nl="en_US"
      arch="x86_64">

   <description url="https://github.com/MAXSONJORDAN/org.knime.htmltablereader">
      HTML Table Reader
This is knime node plug-in ,was developed to read a file and
search for html tables tags like td, th or tr and try convert
it to knime data table.

🚀 About Me
I&apos;m a full stack Web, desktop and Mobile developer... and I have
ability to the learn and apply any dev technologies, in this
case, knime was a temporary necessity where I don&apos;t finded any
solution to read html table file and convert it to knime data
tables.

Authors
@MAXSONJORDAN

Features
Read File HTML with Table and Convert to Knime Data Table
OBS
For this project is required the Lib JSOUP (https://jsoup.org/).
   </description>

   <copyright url="https://github.com/MAXSONJORDAN/org.knime.htmltablereader/blob/main/LICENSE">
      THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES
OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE,
ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER
DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
   </copyright>

   <license url="https://github.com/MAXSONJORDAN/org.knime.htmltablereader/blob/main/LICENSE">
      MIT License

Copyright (c) 2021 Maxson Jordan

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.jsoup"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.knime.htmltablereader"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
